<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="error_removing_social_auth">Could not disconnect authentication method without a backup method.</string>
    <string name="login_validation_error_invalidemail">Please enter a valid E-Mail, that is not already associated with a habitica account.</string>
    <string name="continue_with_google">Continue with Google</string>
    <string name="continue_with_email">Continue with email</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="need_an_account">Need an account?</string>
    <string name="enjoy_getting_things_done">Enjoy having fun getting things done</string>
    <string name="what_should_call_you">What should we call you?</string>
    <string name="get_started">Get Started</string>
    <string name="username_description">This is a unique name you can change later at any time!</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_avatar">You must be new here. I’m Justin, I’ll be your guide in Habitica.\n\nSo how would you like to look? Don’t worry, you can change this later.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_tasks">Looking good! Now, choose any categories you’d like to work on and we’ll create a few tasks. We’ll go to your task board after this!</string>
    <string name="user_data">User Data</string>
    <string name="privacy_preferences">Privacy Preferences</string>
    <string name="privacy_preferences_summary">Change your privacy permissions</string>
    <string name="your_privacy_preferences">Your Privacy Preferences</string>
    <string name="your_privacy_preferences_description"><![CDATA[Your privacy is important to us. Habitica uses data from your device to analyze performance, handle support requests, and provide you with the best possible gamified experience. To do that, we need to request the following permissions.<br /><br />You can change this at any time. To learn more, review our <a href="https://habitica.com/static/privacy">Privacy Policy</a>.]]></string>
    <string name="performance_analytics"><![CDATA[Performance & Analytics]]></string>
    <string name="performance_analytics_description">This is used to improve the user experience, performance, and services of Habitica. Our support team will also use this when handling requests and bug reports.</string>
    <string name="strictly_necessary_analytics">Strictly necessary</string>
    <string name="strictly_necessary_analytics_description">This is necessary data required by our app to function. This includes data like your preferences saved in settings as well as crash information.</string>
    <string name="your_privacy_preferences_description_full">"Habitica uses data from your device to analyze performance, handle support requests, and provide you with the best possible gamified experience. To do that, we need to request the following permissions.\n\nYou can change these at any time from your account settings.</string>
    <string name="accept_all">Accept All</string>
    <string name="habiticas_privacy_policy">Habitica\'s Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="save_preferences">Save Preferences</string>
    <string name="change_subscription_plan">Change your subscription plan</string>
    <string name="change_subscription_duration">Change Subscription Plan</string>
    <string name="continue_current_benefits">Continues current subscription benefits</string>
    <string name="current_plan">Current Plan</string>
    <string name="review_subscription_change_info">You\'ll be able to review upcoming charges before confirming your change in the next step</string>
    <string name="subscriptions_renew_info">Subscriptions automatically renew until cancelled at the price of your newly selected plan.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_subscription">Upgrade Subscription</string>
    <string name="subscribe_again">Subscribe Again</string>
    <string name="complete_purchase">Complete Purchase</string>
    <string name="subscription_renew_review_info">Once we’ve confirmed your purchase, the payment will be charged \nto your Google Account.\n\nSubscriptions automatically renew unless auto-renewal is turned off at least 24-hours before the end of the current period. If you have an active subscription, your account will be charged for renewal within 24-hours prior to the end of your current subscription period and you will be charged the same price you agree to pay above.\n\nBy continuing you accept the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.</string>
</resources>
