<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="tutorial_habits">Complete Positive Habits to earn gold and experience! Negative Habits will hurt your avatar if you tap them, so avoid them in real life!</string>
    <string name="tutorial_dailies">Defeat your repeating Daily tasks to gain gold and experience. Danger! Dailies will hurt your avatar if you don\'t complete them in time.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_todos">Complete your To-Dos in real life, then check them off for GOLD and EXPERIENCE so you can earn Rewards and unlock new features!</string>
    <string name="tutorial_rewards">These are your Rewards! Earn gold by completing real-world Habits, Dailies, and To-Dos. Then spend it on in-game Rewards or custom real-world Rewards!</string>

    <string name="tutorial_equipment">When you buy equipment, it appears here. Your Battle Gear affects your stats, and your Costume (if enabled) affects what your avatar wears.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_items">Earn items by completing tasks and leveling up. Tap on an item to use it!</string>
    <string name="tutorial_pets">As you complete real-world tasks, you now have a random chance of finding eggs and potions. Combine them to hatch pets</string>
    <string name="tutorial_skills">Skills are special abilities that have powerful effects! Tap on a skill to use it. It will cost Mana (the blue bar), which you earn by checking in every day and by completing your real-life tasks. Check out the FAQ in the menu for more info!</string>
    <string name="tutorial_party">This is where you and your friends can hold each other accountable to your goals and fight monsters with your tasks!</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tavern">Welcome to the Tavern, a public, all-ages chatroom! Here you can chat about productivity and ask questions. Have fun!</string>
    <string name="tutorial_classes">Choose to become a Warrior, Mage, Healer, or Rogue! Each class has unique equipment and skills. Tap the (?) to learn more!</string>
</resources>